浦东新区
上海  中国
♬I wish I would have met you.♬
♬Now it's a little late.♬
♬What you could have taught me?♬
♬I could have saved some face.♬
♬They think that your early ending.♬
♬Was all wrong?♬
♬Hey, man.♬
♬Nice shot.♬
需要生物识别
解码失败
计划失败  无法解码信息
The plan failed. We can't decode the message.
打电话给雷蒙德·雷丁顿
Call Raymond Reddington.
《罪恶黑名单》第一季第三集
吴京
第84号
-吴京给你的  -拜托  别在这
- From Wu Jing. - Good God. Not here.
跟我合作的那位先生最近没时间
The gentleman I usually contract with is unavailable --
他在伯利兹的珊瑚礁被蝠鲼咬了一下
Stung by a manta ray off the barrier reef in Belize.
我还认识一个人
I have another tech in mind.
得速战速决
This needs to be done quickly.
-今天  -去找璐丽要我说的人的资料
- Today? - Speak with Luli about the replacement I'm offering.
做好尽职调查
Conduct your due diligence.
如果没问题  就按计划行事
If things are in order, we can proceed as discussed.
我跟自己下棋时不喜欢有人围观
I prefer to play with myself in private.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好  抱歉
Yeah, sorry.
我只是有点心不在焉
I'm just a little distracted.
不  没关系
No, that's -- that's all right.
我只是  坐在这里说我的遭遇
I'm... sitting here talking about what happened to me
好像事情只发生在我身上一样
like it only happened to me.
但其实这事对我俩都有影响
But it happened to us both.
回到家感到有点奇怪  因为
It's just a little weird to be home because...
莉兹  有个人闯进咱家
Lizzy, a man came into our home.
我知道  对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
真希望我能告诉你更多
I wish I could tell you more.
我想告诉你  我
I want to tell you more. I --
那就说  他是谁
So, tell me something. Who was he?
他死了  被杀了
He's gone. He was killed.
所以都结束了
So it's over?
是的
Yes.
我爱你
Look, I love you.
是艾丽
That's Ellie.
我只是很讨厌有些事你不得不瞒着我
I just hate that there are things you have to hide from me.
早上好
Good morning!
你饿了吧  我来做早餐
Hope you're hungry. I'm making breakfast.
不用这么麻烦
Oh, you don't have to do that.
开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
美味的煎蛋卷能治愈一切
A good omelet has healing powers.
布鲁斯和梅莉莎今晚会带晚餐来
Bruce and Melissa are bringing over dinner tonight.
你们真是太好了
That's incredibly cool of you.
朋友被精神病了捅刀子
Hey, friends don't let friends starve
我们不能让他们饿肚子啊
when they've been stabbed by violent psychopaths.
-他怎么样了  -我就坐在这呢
- How's he doing? - I'm sitting right here.
我不是问你
I'm not asking you.
你肯定会说没事的
You'll say fine,
你就是干这个的  你是个好演员
because that's what you do. You're a good actor.
凯伦帮我代课去了
Karen's covering my classes.
我们先吃饭  然后去做理疗
We're gonna eat and then head over to physical therapy.
我得走了  艾丽  我们欠你个人情
I got to run. Ellie, we owe you.
谁说不是
So true.
你知道的  不是迫不得已我是不会走的
You know I wouldn't go if I didn't have to.
不论他们让你干什么
Look, whatever they pulled you into,
你快点解决  我们就可以早点回到正轨
the sooner you get it over with, the sooner we get our life back.
好的
Okay.
拜拜
Bye.
九毫米手枪射出的弹头和弹壳
Slug and casing from a 9-millimeter.
比对一下
Can you run these
看看系统中的记录是否有相匹配的
and see if they match any crimes in our system?
弹道检测室
机会来了
An opportunity has come our way.
昨天中国人在上海杀了一名中情局特工
Yesterday, the Chinese killed a C.I.A. agent in Shanghai.
他们拿走了他的电脑
They took his computer,
以为可以用来破译他们截获的一条信息
which they thought could decode a message they intercepted.
但是不行
It couldn't.
他们让我帮忙
They've asked me to help.
罗德里克是我的老朋友了
Oh, Rodrick is a dear old friend.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你要帮中国人破译中情局的信息吗
You're decoding C.I.A. messages on behalf of the Chinese?
你这话说得好像我是卖国贼
Now, you see, you make it sound like treason.
如此黑白分明  其实不是的  是绿色的
So black and white. It's not. It's green.
事实上  美国的秘密是可以
The fact is, American secrets are for sale
通过各种信誉良好的供应商买卖的  包括我
by an assortment of reputable vendors, myself included.
即使我不做  也会有别人做的
If I don't do this, someone else will.
花钱雇我的人叫吴京
The man who's paying me is called Wu Jing.
你可能听说过他
Perhaps you've heard of him.
他以前在国家安全局工作
Formerly, he worked for the Ministry of State Security.
虽然中国政府没有正式批准
He's not officially sanctioned by the Chinese.
但私底下他干的都是
But unofficially, he's contracted
除掉对手特工的活儿  美国的  英国的
to take out rival agents -- American, British.
要破译的信息里可能有另一名特工的名字
The message likely contains the name of another agent.
你觉得我会相信吗
Do you expect me to believe that --
跟神秘吴京的秘密会面
A secret meeting with the mysterious Wu Jing?
-很有趣  不是吗  -他是虚构的
- Intriguing, isn't it? - He's a myth.
大家也都是这么说深喉和G点的
That's what they said about deep throat and the G-spot.
我向你保证吴京是真实存在的  他雇了我
I assure you Wu Jing is quite real, and he's hired me.
现在你有机会抓住他
Now you have the chance to catch him.
我已经把你的卧底身份给他们了
I've already forwarded them your cover.
什么  什么卧底身份
What? What cover?
卡罗琳·吉文斯
Carolyn Givins,
麻省理工应用物理学博士
PhD in applied physics from M.I.T..
我告诉他们你是我的新加密专家
I've told them you're my new encryption specialist.
你这是让我牺牲一个美国探员的生命
You're asking me to betray the life of an American agent.
听着  这么多年来  情报机构
Listen, this is a guy who the intelligence community
一直在讨论
has been talking about for decades
他是不是虚构的
as if he were a figment.
你们都不知道他是否真实存在
You don't even know if he's real or not.
他是真实存在的  千真万确
Well, he is real -- very.
我现在给你机会抓到他
And I'm giving you the opportunity to grab him.
好消息是他都没在中国
Now, the good news is he's not even in China.
他就在这儿  就在你家后院
He's right here in your own backyard.
如果一切顺利
If we play our cards right,
我还能去里斯本吃个早饭
I can still make Lisbon by breakfast.
罗德里克  两个都要
Rodrick, both.
迈克尔·艾尔瓦拉多  凯文·怀亚特
Michael Alvarado, Kevin Wyatt,
联邦调查局  司法部
布莱斯·詹森
Bryce Jensen.
三个在中国工作的特工  身份都暴露了
Three agents based in China, three covers blown.
据雷丁顿所说
According to Reddington,
都是被一个叫吴京的人所杀
all were murdered by a man named Wu Jing.
-吴京是谁  -中国有个计划生育政策
- Who is Wu Jing? - China has a one-child policy.
据说吴京是二胎
They say that Wu Jing was a second child.
所以他家抛弃了他  否认他出生过
So they gave him away, denied he was ever born.
对他家来说他根本不存在
He was invisible to his family.
对于吴京所从事的工作
Wu Jing made a life working in a business
不存在是个绝佳的优势
where invisibility was an incredible asset.
雷丁顿告诉你他能找到这个人
Reddington's told you he can find this guy?
他称吴京雇他来破译一条
He claims Wu Jing has hired him to decode a message
中国人从中情局截到的信息
that the Chinese have intercepted from the C.I.A.
他认为里面可能有我们
He believes that it might contain the identify
在中国另一个特工的身份
of another one of our assets in China.
我觉得我们该跟进
I think we should move on this.
我没准备好要做这个
I'm not prepared to do this.
我理解你有顾虑
I understand you have reservations.
顾虑
Reservations?
你让我去监视一个臭名昭著的间谍杀手
You're asking me to spy on a notorious spy killer
还要我假装密码专家
while pretending to be an expert in cryptography,
那个领域我一无所知
which I know nothing about.
雷丁顿坚持要你去
Reddington insists on you.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
看看这些照片
Look at those pictures.
如果那条信息里有另一个名字
If there is a name in that message,
那份文件里就会再多一张脸
there's gonna be another face in that file.
那就是你的责任
That'll be on you.
我很快回来  拿一下我的包
I'll be back in a second. I just need to grab my purse.
我以为在台子上呢
I thought it was on the counter.
有人吗
Hello?
找到了吗
Hey. Did you find it?
找到了  不好意思  来了
Oh, yeah, sorry. I'm coming.
如果我做这个  有什么好处
Okay. Say I do this, what's in it for me?
看看你  还要谈条件
Look at you, camel trading like a Bedouin.
如果我帮你  我要有所回报
If I'm gonna help you, I want something in return.
比如
Such as?
真相  就这一次
The truth. Just once.
我想知道你为什么选我
I want to know why you chose me.
好吧  那我们得赶快走了
Well, then, we need to move quickly.
事情已经开始了
Things are already in play.
WDCJ
WDCJ --
是九公里外的一座小型广播站
a small radio station five miles from here.
那幢楼在六年前被一家
The building was purchased six years ago
为中国政府打掩护的公司买了
by a corporation fronting for the Chinese government.
不好意思  等一下
I'm sorry. Wait.
你是说吴京在利用广播站
You're telling us that Wu Jing is running a spy ring
进行间谍活动吗
out of a radio station?
我们会与吴京见面
We'll meet Wu Jing.
你来破译信息并将其传给你的人
You'll decode the message and transmit it to your team.
如果我破译了信息
If I decode the message,
这意味着中国人也会拿到
that means the Chinese get it, too.
就是这样  你和中国人
Exactly -- both you and the Chinese
都会知道这条信息
will know the name of the agent
所涉及的特工名字
for which the message was intended,
然后就是比速度了
and the race begins.
我们要救他  而中国人要杀掉他
We try to save him. The Chinese try to kill him.
-我们可以给他们个虚假信息  -不行
- We could give them a false message. - No.
这个可行  我们可以误导他们
That could work. We could send them in the wrong direction.
我说了不行
I said no.
中国人可能不知道这条信息是什么
The Chinese may not know what the message is,
但是他们肯定会分辨假信息
but they certainly know what it isn't.
要来就来真的  要不然就不做
We do it for real, or we don't do it at all.
计划不错  不过如我所言
Great plan, except, as I have said,
我对加密一窍不通
I know nothing about encryption.
你学东西很快
You're a very quick study.
我认识个人可以帮你
I have a guy who can help you with that.
信息会在一个像这样子的闪存里
你把它插进去
就像个魔盒了
中国人会把截获的信息通过这样的闪存
The Chinese will give you an intercepted message
交给你
on one of these.
把它插进去  它会提示你连接一个数据库
Insert it, and it will prompt you to connect a data locker.
李顺说它就像个魔盒
Shun Lee says it's like a magic box.
魔盒
A magic box?
所以你等一下把它插进去
数据库会自动解密信息
The data locker applies a key to the message.
这需要花一段时间
It'll take a moment,
不过解码后的信息会出现在你的笔记本上
but the decoded message will appear on your laptop.
那我怎么把信息提取出来
How do I get the message out?
你不用  电脑会帮你做
You don't. The computer does it for you.
你需要的就是一个卫星信号
All you need is a satellite connection.
如果你有问题你把这个插进去
这就是我自己做的
如果没有卫星信号  就用这个
If you don't have a satellite connection, use this.
这是一个远程镜像程序
It's a remote mirroring program.
可以让我们的技术员在外部控制系统
It'll give our tech on the outside control of the system.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
我讲得怎么样
很棒  你的普通话太赞了
Great. You're rocking the Mandarin.
谢谢
Xie xie.
长官  还有三分钟就到会面时间了
Three minutes till the meeting, sir.
雷丁顿到底在哪  他迟到了
Where the hell is Reddington? He's late.
他会搞砸这事的
He's gonna blow this whole damn thing.
你抽烟吗
Do you smoke?
-不抽  -现在你抽了
- No. - Well, you do now.
或者至少你正在戒烟
Or at least you're trying to quit.
这是中情局全新的设备
This is C.I.A. equipment. It's brand-new.
看起来像尼古丁贴片
It looks like a nicotine patch,
但却是个非常敏感的发射器
but it's a very sensitive transmitter.
270米的传送范围  是塑料聚合物
It has a range of 300 yards, and it's a plastic polymer,
检验器验不出来
which means it won't show up if it gets wanded.
你要是错了怎么办
And if you're wrong?
我不会错
I'm not wrong.
他到底在哪里
Where the hell is he?
他应该一小时前就到
He was supposed to be here an hour --
我们还在等什么
What are we waiting for?
一号监视点  就位了吗
Surveillance one, are you in position?
收到  已经就位
Roger that. In position.
卫星信号良好  运行正常
Satellite feed up and running.
这边请
Right this way.
开始了
Here we go.
先生  抱歉  这是规定
Sorry, sir. Protocol.
女士请上前
Miss, please.
谢谢  先生请上前
Thank you. Sir?
国防高研计划局的8毫米跟踪芯片
DARPA tracking chip, 8-millimeter tag.
我去年三月被索马里海盗抓走了
I was taken by Somali pirates last March,
在船运集装箱里待了三个星期
spent three weeks in a shipping container.
头两个星期噩梦一般
The first two were a nightmare.
第三个星期还挺不错的
The third one was actually quite pleasant.
虽然如此  不会再来一次了
Even so, that won't happen again.
你要是有干净的剃须刀片和吗啡
If you have a clean razor blade and some morphine,
我可以拿掉
I'll remove it.
没必要  但你的同事
That won't be necessary, but I am going to need
要接受指纹扫描
a biometric print scan from your associate.
-她是和我一起的  -明白
- She's with me. - Understood.
但我收到指示要扫描任何新访客
But my orders are to scan any new visitors.
是和什么数据库进行比对的
What database is this being run against?
所有的数据库
All of them.
指纹分析中
发生了什么事
What's happening?
他们在查她的指纹
They are running her prints.
-能拦截吗  -不知道
- Can you intercept them? - I don't know.
原来你们喜欢灰色
So, you went with the gray?
好了
Okay.
消除了
Vanish.
找不到匹配记录
跟我来
Follow me.
如你所见  我们做了些改进
As you can see, we've made some improvements.
你那追踪芯片到里面就失效了
Oh, your DARPA chip won't work where you're going.
到了后吴京会给你们解释
Wu Jing will explain when you get there.
到哪里
Get where?
信号丢失
发生了什么
What the hell just happened?
信号丢失
-没信号了  -不可能就这样消失了
- We lost them. - We can't just lose them.
出了什么问题
What happened to our signal?
他们好像在下降
They seem to be descending,
这没道理啊
which doesn't make any sense.
建筑图纸上没有地下空间
The blueprints don't show any underground space.
把信号找回来
Get that signal back.
你觉得我们会下降多深
How far down do you think we're going?
足够深
Far enough.
我的朋友
My friend.
不必假惺惺的  吴京  你一个朋友都没有
Don't be cheeky, Wu Jing. You don't have any friends.
这是我的同事
My associate.
吉文斯女士
Ms. Givins.
罗宾斯教授只和顶尖人才合作
Professor Robins only works with the best.
他是个了不起的老师
Oh, he was an amazing teacher.
听说他去世了我很遗憾
I was so sorry to hear that he passed away.
你这里做了些改进
You've made some changes.
-我们不得不加强安保  -我能想象
- We had to increase security. - I can imagine --
过去一年半里有四个美国特工被杀
Four American agents killed in the past year and a half.
你一定很忙
You've been busy.
我猜这里屏蔽了一切
I presume nothing gets in or out,
无论是无线电还是卫星传送
no radio or satellite transmissions.
只能凭信任进出
Nothing but trust.
请别介意
Please don't take offense.
这是为了避免被美国人侦听
I can't risk American surveillance.
只有我们的系统通过硬接线与外界连接
Only our systems are hard-wired to the outside world.
开始工作吧
Let's get to work.
我曾在一个地洞里有过很糟糕的经历
I once had a bad experience in a deep hole in the ground.
金隼  新的高级译码员
Jin Sun, my new senior cryptographer.
我们本以为是标准RSA加密算法
We expected standard RSA encryption,
但这个更复杂
but this was something stronger.
政府在实验
The government's been experimenting
更好的因子分解算法
with better factoring algorithms.
淘汰RSA算法是早晚的事
It's only a matter of time before RSA's obsolete.
你说得对
You're right. It is.
我需要一点时间安装设备
I'll just need a few moments to set up my equipment.
这边请
This way.
他们在弄  但还没结果
They're trying, but still nothing.
可能是中国人干扰了我们的信号
Either the Chinese are scrambling our signals,
信号丢失
或者莉斯和红魔超出了追踪范围
or Liz and Red are out of range.
我记得你的设备追踪范围是270米
I thought your equipment had a range of 300 yards.
是的  但也许他们在大楼下
It does, but maybe they've built a bunker
挖了个地下室
that deep under the building.
信号丢失
我们被耍了
We're getting played.
红魔和莉兹是故意让信号失灵的
That signal went dark because Red and Liz wanted it to.
不太可能
That's not likely.
我们有多少时间找出确切原因
How long can we wait to find out?
也许是他们有危险呢
Is it possible they could be in danger?
所以我们更加不能这么等下去
That's another reason not to wait.
让所有突击小组待命
Keep all insertion teams on standby.
五分钟后还没有基恩探员的消息就冲进去
If we don't hear from Agent Keen in five minutes, we're going in.
准备好了吗
We ready yet?
需要卫星信号
你常回家吗  金隼
Do you get home much, Jin Sun?
两年没回去了
Not for two years.
那可真不容易  要是我肯定会很痛苦
Oh, that must be hard. It certainly would be for me.
我连手机都没有
I don't even have a phone.
我坚持亲自传递一切消息
I insist on delivering all of my messages in person.
需要卫星信号
没时间人工传递
探员会被杀害
你的家乡在哪个省
What province are you from?
云南省
From Yunnan.
那可是个美丽的地方
Oh, beautiful part of the country.
我之前在昆明市郊的一个庙里
I spent a month in silent meditation
花了一个月的时间冥想
at a monastery just outside of Kunming.
需要卫星信号
没时间人工传递
探员会被杀害
必须用金的电脑
怎么办
那真是一次很好的
It was a wonderful escape
逃离尘世的体验
from the distractions of everyday life.
我都没法想象呆在这下面会有多让人心烦
I can't imagine the distractions one might encounter down here.
你觉得呢
Can you?
是啊  无法想象
No. I can't.
必须用金的电脑
怎么办
没错  分散他们的注意力
很好
Excellent.
我觉得差不多准备好了  这应该很有意思
I think we're almost ready. This should be fun.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
我发誓  如果你让我再碰到跟上次
I swear, if I run into the same trouble
在香港一样的状况
I had with you in Hong Kong...
我们认识这么多年了
In all the years you and I have known each other,
我可从来没让你陷入这样的境地
I've never put you in a position like this.
你知道我怎么做生意的
You know how I conduct my business.
我可不想惹上这些麻烦
I don't need this kind of crap.
你向我保证这里肯定安全
You assured me this place was secure.
-是很安全 -那是什么
- It is. - Then what the hell is that?!
那辆厢式货车
That van.
我们到的时候它就在那里了  现在还在
It was there when we arrived, and it's still there.
肯定是联邦调查局
That is the FBI.
弄了那么多扫描检查
With all the scans and wands
还建了这个连接到中土世界的电梯
and this elevator you've built that goes down to middle earth,
你们居然没去检查一下
and you don't even bother to sweep the street
这周边的街道  真是太扯了
around your building? This is nonsense.
-冷静点  朋友  -你被监视了
- Calm down, old friend. - You're under surveillance!
如果联调局在外边  那也是你引来的
If the FBI was outside, it's because you led them here.
这20年我在全球各地
I've been moving comfortably through the world
来去自如  无影无踪
for the past 20 years without a trace.
难道现在几个不入流的间谍杀手
And now some two-bit spy killer
就想置我和我的事业于险境吗
is gonna put my life and business in jeopardy?
外面那辆面包车
看看怎么回事
有情况  所有人注意
We have activity. Everybody, heads up.
被发现了  你两点钟方向  15秒内撤离
We're made. Your 2 o'clock. Break it down. 15 seconds.
该走了  收起来
We got to go. Pack it up.
你
You!
-我们暴露了  -有可能
- They know we're here. - Maybe,
也有可能只是
or maybe the van's just
这货车停太久引起他们的警觉了
been there too long and they're being careful.
我不喜欢这样  等我信号就进去
I don't like it. We're going in on my signal.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
看到没  什么都没有
You see? Nothing.
可以继续了吗
Now...can we continue?
你真该为自己感到羞耻
You should be ashamed of yourself.
置我和吉文斯女士于险境  太不专业了
To put Ms. Givins and I at risk, it's unprofessional.
-我不能忍了  -够了
- I've reached my limit. - Enough!
什么
What?
好吧  好吧  对不起
Okay. Okay. You know, I'm sorry.
我今天不太顺
I've had a rough day.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
可以开始了吗
Should we do this?
出发  1分钟后到达
Let's roll. E.T.A. -- one minute.
信息在这里面
The message.
你不怀念那些
Don't you miss the good old days
用公用电话和险中逃生的美好时光吗
with the pay phones and the brush pasts?
还剩30秒
30 seconds out.
等等  我收到了一些东西
Wait. I've got something.
她在用远程镜像程序
She's using the remote mirroring program.
米拉的联系人给她的
Meera's contact gave her.
等等  这不是她的电脑
Uh, hang on. This isn't her computer.
看起来是个中文系统
It looks like one of the Chinese systems.
有中情局的信息吗
Can you see the C.I.A. message?
是的  长官  还不止那些  正在下载
Yes, sir, and a lot more than that. Downloading now.
-还剩10秒  -所有单位  撤退
- 10 seconds out. - Okay, all units, stand down.
重复  撤退
I repeat, stand down.
重复  所有单位  撤退
I repeat, all units stand down.
撤退中
Standing down.
这是你下一个目标  第五个要干掉的人
There's your next target -- kill number five.
亨利·周
Henry Cho.
收到信息了  目标是亨利·周
We have the message. The target is Henry Cho.
好  抓紧时间
All right. The clock is ticking.
把这人的所有资料都找出来
I want everything we can find on this guy.
信息是从中情局服务器
This was sent from a C.I.A. server,
发到南京古南都饭店的服务器的
delivered to a server at the Nanjing Grand Hotel.
周先生  为什么中情局要往你住的酒店
So, Mr. Cho, why is the C.I.A. sending you secret messages
发秘密信息呢
at your hotel?
等等  这个人不是探员
Hold on. This guy's not an agent.
他是中美混血  一名建筑师
He's Chinese-American, an architect.
建筑师
An architect?
那他怎么和中情局扯上关系的
Then why the hell is he talking to the C.I.A.?
因为我们找他帮忙
Because we asked for his help.
亨利·周在中库建筑公司工作
Henry Cho works for Zhongku Construction.
不是在中国  是在华盛顿特区
Not in China, here in D.C.
中库  那可是家很大的建筑公司
Zhongku -- they're a huge construction company.
美国司法部  联邦调查局
他们设计的建筑遍布世界各地
They design buildings all over the world.
他的出入境档案显示他在过去十个月中
His immigration file says he's been to the company headquarters
六次前往公司总部
6 times in the last 10 months.
那就是中情局接触他的原因
That's why the C.I.A. reached out to him.
中库正在为上海设计一座新的政府大楼
Zhongku's designing a new government building in Shanghai.
我们请亨利利用他的权限帮我们拿到图纸
We asked Henry to use his access to get us the plans.
多亏他  我们窃听了整幢军委大楼
Thanks to him, our ops bugged the entire city military commission.
咱们把话说明白
Let me get this straight.
这个人不是训练有素的特工
This guy's not a trained operative.
他只是一名  承包商
He's just a... contractor?
一个平民
A civilian.
他现在在哪里
Where is he now?
就在这里
Here.
入境档案显示他三天之前离开中国
Immigration says he left China three days ago,
飞行记录
乘机抵达杜勒斯机场
a return flight to Dulles Airport.
谢谢你  阿兰姆  不用谢
Thank you, Aram. You're welcome.
找到他
Go get him.
-中库建筑公司  -请转亨利·周
- Zhongku Construction. - Henry Cho, please.
我需要立刻和他通话  是非常重要的事情
It's very important that I speak to him immediately.
他的兄弟  小平  出了车祸
His brother, Xiaoping, has been in a car accident.
他和他的儿子在我们费尔围的楼那边
He's at our Fairview Property with his son.
我可以试试给他打电话
I can try to call him --
找到姓周的  干掉他
他不接电话
There's no answer on his cell.
给公司打电话  问问他在哪
Call the company. Find out where he is.
我的朋友  多少感谢都不够
My friend, I can't thank you enough.
这些就够了
This is all the thanks I require.
拿上你的东西  是时候离开了
Get your things. It's time to go.
别管了
Leave it.
封锁出入口
Lock it down.
站住
Stop!
你是对的
You were right.
也许外面是联调局的人
Maybe that was the F.B.I. outside.
事实上  也许他们不止在外面
In fact, maybe they're not just outside.
也许他们就在这间屋子里
Maybe they're right here in this room.
要指控别人之前  先自己想清楚
Think hard before you accuse anybody of anything.
几分钟之前
A few minutes ago,
有人在这里连上了联调局的服务器
contact was made from this room to an FBI server.
我付出如此努力劫来的信息
A message I worked so hard to intercept
被传送给了美国人
was sent to the Americans.
我的直觉告诉我是她干的
Well, all my instincts said it was her.
我很相信我的直觉
I trust my instincts.
你很聪明
You're smart.
干这事的人很聪明
The one responsible was smart,
但是我们的系统更聪明
but our systems are smarter.
任何与政府服务器的连接都会被标记以供检查
Any contact with a government server is flagged for review.
所以
So...
我知道是谁背叛了我们
I know who betrayed us.
他不在办公室
He's not at the office.
他跟一个客户在费尔围和华莱士街交口的楼里
He's with a client at a property at Fairview and Wallace.
再给他打一遍
Try him again.
这里  会有几扇窗
So, over here, they're gonna make some windows.
外面这里
And out here...
会是个露台
there's gonna be a balcony
露台会横跨整座楼
that runs the length of the whole build--
-你说过要吃冰激凌的  -好的
- You said we were gonna get ice cream. - Okay.
我先给你看点别的东西
Let me just show you something else first.
把他拉起来
Get him up.
-我还以为你很忠心呢  -我不明白
- I thought you were loyal to us. - I don't understand.
信息是从你的系统传出去的  金隼
The message was sent from your system, Jin Sun.
这  这不可能
T-that's not possible.
不可能
That's not possible.
就是如此  而且不止是那信息
It is, and not just one message.
你把所有东西都给他们了
You gave them everything,
包括我们研究了几个月的文件
files we've worked on for months!
别人都没有权限
Nobody else had access.
我们得阻止他们
We have to do something.
安静
Quiet.
我们不能让他们这么干
We can't just let them do this.
你背叛了我
背叛了国家
把秘密卖给美国人
你不觉得害臊吗
你
You --
尽管这场面挺有意思的
As entertaining as all this has been,
但我们真的得走了
we really do need to leave now.
联调局马上就会来找你们了
The next sound you hear is gonna be the FBI knocking on your door,
而我  决不能留在这里
and I, for one, am not gonna be here.
吴京  看着我
Wu Jing! Look at me!
你杀了我的人
You don't kill one of my people.
现在我也要杀一个你的人
Now I have to kill one of yours.
从他发送消息的那一刻起
The moment he sent that message,
他对你就没用了
he became worthless to you.
你会再揍他二十分钟
You would have beaten him for another 20 minutes
然后亲手杀了他
and then killed him yourself.
但如果我让你杀死我的人
But if I let you kill a contractor of mine,
以后就没人会信任我了
I'll lose the trust of all my others,
也就没生意好做了
and that's just bad business.
所以如果你要杀她  最好把我也杀了
So if you kill her, you better kill me.
否则我就要杀了你
Or I'm going to kill you.
你雇我干活  我干完了
You hired me to do a job. It's done.
现在离开这吧
Now let's get out of here.
跟我来
Follow me.
还有一条出路
I have another way out.
我们去吃冰激凌  好吗
Let's go get you some ice cream, all right?
好
Okay.
喂
Hello?
周先生  我是中情局的米拉·马丽科特工
Mr. Cho, this is Agent Meera Malik with the C.I.A.
中情局  我不明白
C.I.A.? I don't understand.
你们不该打我这个电话的
You're not supposed to be calling me on this line.
听我说  你现在有危险
Listen to me. You are in danger.
听清了吗  中国人知道你名字了
Can you hear me? The Chinese have your name.
有人往你那里去了
There are men on their way to your location.
-我们在12层  -待在那儿别动
- We're on the 12th floor. - Stay where you are.
我们来救你
We're coming to get you.
躲好  我们很快就到
Stay hidden. We're just minutes out.
爸爸
Dad?
过来  过来  我们走
Come here. Come here. Let's go.
我在这苦心经营了三年
I've been building this place for three years,
现在却毁于一旦
and now my operation is burned.
那就再弄一个
So build another.
长官  找到他们了
Sir, I've got them.
红魔脖子里的芯片刚刚上线
The microchip in Red's neck just came online
还有我们放在基恩探员身上的窃听器
and the bug we put on Agent Keen.
他们离开了那幢楼  正在丹佛斯路向西行驶
They're out of the building, moving west on Danforth.
他们要去哪里
Where the hell are they going?
派特工拦截他们
Just send agents to intercept them.
藏好  藏好
Get underneath. Get underneath.
听我说
Listen. Listen.
别动  知道吗
Don't move, all right?
千万别动
Just don't move.
把手放好
No, put your hand in.
喂  回来
已经没有机会走了
不
No!
住手  爸爸
Stop! Dad!
爸爸  爸爸
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
放开他  放开我儿子
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Let him go! Let my son go!
拜托了  放了我儿子
Please! Please! Just let my son go! Please!
没事的  没事的  我什么都愿意做
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay. I'll do anything.
放了他吧  不会有事的
Just let him go. It's gonna be all right.
-不会有事的  我保证  -爸爸
- It's gonna be all right. I promise. I promise. - Dad!
雷斯勒  这边搞定了
Ressler, clear!
雷斯勒  没事吧
Ressler, clear?
我没事  谢谢
I'm good. Thanks.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你为我们所做的一切
Thank you for all you've done for us.
我可以带大家离开这个国家
I can get us out of the country.
那真是太好了
That's very kind,
但我确信我们可以自己应付
but I'm sure we can muddle through on our own.
找个阴凉处停车就好
Anywhere in the shade up here would be fine.
恐怕会让你失望了
I fear I've disappointed you.
我们说好的是
The deal was for us
抓到黑名单上的罪犯
to actually catch the criminals on the blacklist,
而现在吴京已经差不多半只脚踏进北京了
and now Wu Jing is as good as halfway to Beijing.
我看未必
I don't think so.
-没事吧  -没事
- Is everything okay? - We're fine.
快  快  举起手来
Move! Move! Let me see your hands!
下车  下车  下车
Get out! Get out! Get out!
-靠在车上  -拦截成功
- Up on the car! - The package is secure.
嫌犯已被扣押
Suspect in custody now.
璐丽跟我一起
Luli can stay with me.
邓比会载你去你想去的地方
Dembe will take you wherever you need to go.
你没必要杀他
You didn't have to kill him.
为了确保你的生命安全
I believe I will always do
不管什么事  我都会义无反顾去做的
whatever I feel I have to do to keep you alive.
我该做的都已经做了  现在该你了
I held up my end of the deal. Now it's your turn.
你还没告诉我答案
You owe me an answer.
问题是什么
What's the question?
为什么是我
Why me?
因为你父亲
Because of your father.
什么意思
What does that mean?
你认识我父亲吗
Did you know my father?
你们俩在哪见过面吗
Have the two of you met somehow?
我希望答案可以像问题那样简单
I wish the answer were as simple as the question seems.
但事实上  你的问题同样不简单
But the truth is, the question isn't simple, either.
我能体会你的沮丧
I share your frustration.
你搞得咱俩一样似的  你错了
You act like we're the same. You're wrong.
我有我的生活  有人关心我
I have a life, people who care about me.
可是你  这就是你的全部
But you... This is all you have.
我有你
I have you.
你还好吗
You okay?
凑合吧
I'll live.
听着  我只是想说
Look, I just wanted to say, uh...
也许我以前对你有一些质疑
Maybe I've had some doubts about you.
而且我也没把这些想法隐藏起来
Maybe I haven't done the best job of keeping them to myself,
但你今天做得真的很棒
but what you did today was good work.
谢谢
Thanks.
要不是你传出的那条消息
If you didn't get that message out when you did,
亨利·周肯定活不了
Henry Cho wouldn't be alive.
不管在里边发生了什么事
Whatever else went down in there,
你都不该自责
you should feel good about that.
弹道测试报告
♬Caught in a riptide♬
♬I was searching for the truth♬
♬There was a reason♬
♬I collided into you♬
♬Calling your name in the midnight hour♬
弹道测试报告
♬Reaching for you from the endless dream♬
♬So many miles between us now♬
弹道测试报告
♬That you are always here with me♬
你说得对
You were right.
莉斯·基恩确实有所隐瞒
Liz Keen is hiding something.
我对她进行了标记
I put a flag on her.
任何测试  报告  文件
Any tests, reports, or files--
任何她要的文件  都会先发给我们
Anything she requests gets sent to us first.
她拿了一枚子弹和弹壳去做弹道测试
She brought a bullet and a shell casing into ballistics.
以她的权限  结果显示为机密信息
At her level, the results were classified.
完整报告在这里
But that's the full report.
这不仅仅是机密
This isn't just classified.
关于这起凶杀案的简报
Any briefings on this homicide
都要上报国土安全部部长
include the Secretary of Homeland Security.
还有谁知道此事
Who else knows about this?
♬Calling your name in the midnight hour♬
♬Reaching for you from the endless dream♬
♬So many miles between us now♬
♬That you are always here with me♬
♬With me♬
-你好吗  -挺好的
- How are you? - Good.
-那就好  -我帮你放好这个
- Great. - Let me take this for you.
大家都想来看看汤姆
Everyone wanted to be here for Tom.
都还好吗
Everything go okay?
很好
Fine.
谢谢
Thank you.
吃千层面前我们能不能先谈谈
Hey, can we, um, talk for a second, pre-lasagna?
我想为早上的事道歉
I just wanted to apologize for this morning.
-没事的  -不不  是我错了
- It's okay. - No, no, no. I was wrong.
那是你的工作
It's your job, and, uh,
你工作上有些事情需要保密
I understand if there are certain secrets
我能理解
that you have to keep right now,
没事的
and that's okay.
因为我们会一如既往地挺过去的
Because-- because we'll survive, like always.
我只想让你...  我爱你
I just want you to-- I-I love you.
我得去看人做千层面了
I got to see a man about some lasagna.
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：重案组李sir  圈圈  宝宝  催眠大师  Silence
翻译：hadessl  王大可写两遍  持久君  MythCreator
翻译：Michael  卫老哥  行尸lulu  No.Zero
时间轴：阿阿阿包 Kallen 宝宝 No.Zero
初校：丢丢曳 重案组李sir 卫老哥 圈圈   精校：紫玉
后期：宝宝  MythCreator   总监：紫玉